

CONTACT

Bangkok, Thailand 097 294 5114 viranda.soonthornpakdee@gmail.com www.linkedin.com/in/viranda-s

MY PROFILE

My Name is Viranda Soonthornpakdee, 26 years old. I have designing experience in the Digital Industry more than 4 years, I worked as UX/UI Designer and got promoted to Project Manager/Product Owner in 2018. My strengths are solid organizational skills including attention to detail and multi-tasking skills, strong aptitude and desire to learn new technologies and tools.



SKILLS

- · Software Project Management
- · Web Design
- UI / UX Design
- · Software Design
- HTML/CSS
- · Presentation Design

SOFTWARE SKILLS

- · Adobe Experience Design
- Adobe Photoshop
- Adobe Illustration
- · Bootstrap Studio
- Sketch App
- Figma
- Zeplin
- Keynote

INTERESTS

- · Design Trends
- HTML/CSS
- New Technologies and Tools
- · Social Media Marketing

EXPERIENCE

2018 -Now

PROJECT MANAGER/PRODUCT OWNER (BANGKOK SOLUTIONS CO.,LTD.)

As a Project Manager with designing background, my responsibility are handling, coordinating and managing many types of tasks with other teams, such as web design, application design and software design & development, to accomplish project's timeline.

2016 -Now

SENIOR UX/UI DESIGNER (BANGKOK SOLUTIONS CO.,LTD.)

As an UX/UI Designer, I have been designed with understanding, and passion for pixel-perfect precision to meet customers' requirements and also provided the best solution with great user experience.

And I'm working closely to developer team so I am understand the depth of their working process and able to ensure scope, requirement and direction of the product are aligned and will be handed to customer on time. I have some knowledge about HTML, CSS and database tables, so I can help the developer to edit code which would be reduce developer's tasks.

2015

WEB DESIGNER TRAINEE (DNA AGENCY)

I got internship at DNA Agency as a Web designer for 4 Months and I learned about Web design and Web animate with many company such as AIS and Sumsung.

EDUCATION

2012 -2015

BACHELOR OF FINE AND APPLIED ARTS

Burapha University

2009 -2012

ENGLISH - JAPANESE LANGUAGE AND LITERATURE

Satrinonthaburi